That's not an answer!
（英梨々）何も答えてない！→
倫也。　さっきから
何にも答えてくれない！
Tomoya, you haven't given me a single straight answer all day!
（詩羽）おはよう　倫理君。
Good morning, Mr. Ethical.
Relax. Everything will be okay now.
（詩羽）落ち着きなさい。
もう大丈夫よ。
いや　まさに　今　この状況が→
Uh, this situation is actually anything but okay.
大丈夫じゃないんですが
何で　詩羽先輩が　ここに？
Why are you here, Utaha-senpai?
（詩羽）そんなの　前回　まったく→
Because I had zero screen time in
the previous episode, obviously.
出番が　なかったからに
決まってるでしょう。
それ　全然
理由になってないよね。
That's not a reason!
ていうか　前回って何？
出番って何？
And what's "screen time" supposed to mean?!
What's "previous episode" supposed to mean?!
≪（ドアの開く音）
（恵）あっ　起きたんだ　安芸君。
Oh, you're awake, Aki-kun.
あっ　ちょっと！　先輩　何を！
Senpai, what are you doing?!
うっ　うわ！
見てないで　止めて　加藤！
Don't just stand and watch!
Stop her, Katou!
Yeah... right.
Whenever we're together in the classroom after school
houkago futari de sugoshita kyoushitsu
You at your desk, just talking and talking on and on
tsukue no ue muchuu de hazumu kimi no koe
You're so dense, and it really shows
donkan na kimi no sono taido ga
And that's why I always have to pick on you
itsumo watashi wo ijiwaru ni saseru no
Sometimes I feel like I'm alone
hitoribocchi da to omou toki mo aru
Some days I can't stop myself from crying
namida tomerarenai hi mo aru
I want you to look and see the real me
hontou no watashi wo mitsumete hoshii no
I'll keep believing that one day you will
kitto tsutawaru to shinjiteiru yo
But you just never, ever, never, ever change, and so
kimi wa itsudatte itsudatte kawaranai kara
I keep sending and sending and sending and sending the same signal
watashi ga nankai mo nankai mo signal okutteageru
Dreaming of the day I'll make it over that hill
yume mita ano oka mezashite
Even when I feel like giving up, I can keep going on
kujikesou na toki mo ganbaresou da yo
Because you're there for me
kimi ga iru kara
I see. So Katou called you here, Utaha-senpai.
On an Individual Route for the First Time in Eight Years
そっか。
加藤が　詩羽先輩を呼んだのか。
（詩羽）それは　ともかく→
Setting that aside,
isn't your casually entering his house
an issue worth discussing, Katou-san?
なぜ　あなたが　当然のように
上がり込んでいたのかは→
議論の余地があるけどね。
加藤さん。
I could say the same about you.
霞ヶ丘先輩こそ　「安芸君が大変」
って言っただけで→
Isn't it more concerning that you rushed to get here
within 15 minutes of me saying "Aki-kun is in trouble"?
たった１５分で
駆け付けてきたことに→
議論の余地はないですか？
それで　何があったの？
So, what happened?
何って…。
What do you mean?
Katou-san gave me the gist of what happened,
（詩羽）実際にあったことは
だいたい加藤さんから聞いたけど。
あなたと澤村さんが　どうして
そういう状況になったのかは→
but I'm not going to understand how you
and Sawamura-san ended up in this situation
あなたの口から聞かないと
分からない。
unless I hear the words from your mouth.
あっ…。
（詩羽）さあ　話してごらんなさい。
Come on, out with it.
（詩羽）そして　みんなで
解決策を考えていきましょう。
Then we'll think of a way to fix it.
But this is between me and Eriri.
けど　これは
英梨々と俺の問題だし→
I can't drag you into it.
詩羽先輩まで巻き込むわけには…。
いい？　加藤さん。
What you see here, Katou-san,
is a textbook example of the wimpy protagonist
so common in the world of dating sims.
これがギャルゲー世界によくいる
ヘタレ主人公というやつよ。
ちょっと　トラブルがあると→
When faced with the slightest problem,
he makes a show of indecisive worrying,
あからさまに
うじうじ　悩んで見せて→
and then annoys those around him
by dragging them into it.
周りも巻き込んで
イライラさせるの。
If you're going to become a main heroine,
あなたも　メインヒロインになるのなら
こういう　やからと　これからも→
you'll have to deal with his sort in the future,
付き合っていかなくちゃ
ならないから→
so observe his behavior closely.
よく　観察しておきなさい。
Wow, that sounds like a hassle.
うわ～　それは　めんどくさいかも。
Uh, excuse me, but this is something I'm genuinely troubled by.
あの　すいません。
俺　真剣に悩んでるんですけど。
I understand.
（詩羽）なるほど。　つまり　あなたが
波島さんの本を絶賛したら→
So basically, after you sang praises
for Hashima-san's book,
Sawamura-san flew off the handle
for some reason, berating Hashima-san,
どういうわけか
澤村さんがキレて→
彼女を　散々　ののしって
本を　ビリビリに引き裂いた揚げ句→
tearing her books to shreds, and eventually...
泥の水たまりに突き飛ばして→
shoving her into a mud puddle,
laughing with her posse at Hashima-san.
取り巻きと一緒に
高笑いしていた…　と？
Correct?
At some point that turned into
a certain someone's work of fiction,
途中から　完全に
誰かさんの創作ですけど→
but the beginning was essentially accurate.
序盤は　まあ　そのとおりです。
That's rather immature.
（詩羽）大人げないわね　それは。
ええ　本当に。
Yeah, that's for sure.
あいつ　自分が大物同人作家だって自覚がないんですよ。
Her behavior doesn't seem at all
like that of a big shot doujinshi artist.
大人げないのは　あなたでしょ。
I was referring to you.
お…　俺！？
何も　わざわざ→
M-Me?!
Was it really necessary to praise
someone else's book in front of Sawamura-san?
澤村さんの目の前で　他人の本を
褒める必要なんてあったのかしら。
（詩羽）彼女に何を聞かれても
適当に言葉を濁して→
Regardless of what she had asked,
wouldn't things have turned out better
本当の気持ちは　あなたの中に→
if you had evaded the question and
kept how you actually felt to yourself.
しまっておけば
よかったんじゃないかしら。
それは…　できません。
That's... not something I can do.
俺は　面白かったものを
面白くないとは言えない。
I can't say that something is less
than great when I think otherwise.
出海ちゃんの同人誌や
詩羽先輩の小説を→
I'd sooner quit being an otaku than say that
Izumi-chan's doujinshi or your novels are boring.
つまんないって言うくらいなら
オタクなんか　やめた方がマシだ。
（詩羽）ん…　けっけっけっ…　けど。
B-Be that as it may...
うん？
（詩羽）けど　澤村さんにとっては→
your words to Sawamura-san
came as a fatal blow to her.
あなたの　その言葉は
致命的だった。
Nothing I say could make a dent in Eriri's popularity or ability.
俺が　何を言ったところで
英梨々の人気や実力は→
揺らいだりなんかしないよ。
でも　彼女の心は揺らいだ。→
But it certainly made a dent in her heart.
This might possibly even leave her unable to draw.
もしかしたら　これがきっかけで
描けなくなるかもしれない。
まさか　そんな…。
It couldn't be that bad.
きっと　澤村さんは　何もかも
奪われたって思ったのね。
Sawamura-san must have felt as though everything had been stolen from her.
何もかもって…。
What do you mean, "everything"?
クリエーターとしての尊厳も
幼なじみというポジションも。→
Her dignity as a creator, as well as
her position as the childhood friend.
だって　波島さん
倫理君に　あんなに懐いてて→
I mean, Hashima-san is so attached to you,
she's like a heroine who despite appearing so late in
the story, starts off with an extremely high affection stat.
まるで　途中から登場するくせに→
初期好感度が
ものすごく高くて→
The kind who confesses her love for the protagonist
after he fails to conquer his preferred girl.
狙った女の子の攻略に失敗しても
必ず告白してくるような…。→
何それ　ムカつく。
隠し救済ヒロインなんて→
That makes me so angry.
A crappy hidden fallback heroine should
know her place and stay hidden until the end!
最後まで隠れてればいいのに…。
先輩　あちっ　あちちっ。
Senpai!
（引っかく音）
かはっ！
まあ　そんなわけで
このサークル崩壊の危機を→
Well, in any event, if this circle is to
overcome this threat to its very existence,
乗り越えるには
倫理君が頑張るしかないわ。
you're going to have to work hard, Mr. Ethical.
What do you think I should I do?
俺　どうすればいいのかな。
（詩羽）幼なじみヒロインを
攻略するのよ。→
Conquer the childhood friend heroine,
Mr. Wimpy Protagonist—
ヘタレ主人公君…
いえ　倫理君。
Mr. Ethical, rather.
今の　本当なら
いいシーンだったのに→
That would've made for a
touching scene, but you ruined it.
台無しですね。
Hazy memories, fond recollections, and promises made as children...
遠い記憶とか　懐かしい思い出とか子供のころの約束とか→
Exploit every advantage of childhood friends in the book to raise Sawamura-san's flags.
そういう幼なじみの
アドバンテージを　全部使って→
澤村さんのフラグを立てなさい。
You think she'll fall for something that obvious?
そんな　見え見えの手に
引っ掛かるかな　あいつ。
大丈夫だと思うよ。
I think it'll work fine.
Rather than playing the protagonist,
you need to play the heroine in this scenario.
安芸君が主人公じゃなくて
ヒロインになればいいんだよ。
≪（ノック）
≪（小百合）英梨々！　それじゃ
私とパパは　行ってくるわね。
Eriri, your dad and I are about to leave, okay?
≪（小百合）夏コミ　３日目　最終日。聖なる戦いの日！→
The finale of Summer Comiket, day three!
The day of the sacred battle!
Yes, off to indulge in the male-oriented genre!
そう！
灼熱の男性向け創作ジャンルへと。
（英梨々）いってらっしゃい。
Have fun.
≪（小百合）ああ　そうそう
それで　今夜のパーティーは…。
Oh, and about the party tonight...
I know.
（英梨々）分かってる。　パパの顔
つぶすわけにはいかないもんね。
I wouldn't dream of embarrassing Dad.
ンフフ…。
You're heading out already?
（恵）もう出掛けるの？
Yeah, I better go.
ああ。　行くよ。
夏コミ　３日目　東Ａ２７６
「ｅｇｏｉｓｔｈｉｃ－ｌｉｌｙ」に。
Summer Comiket day three.
East A276, Egoistic Lily.
（恵）澤村さん　会場に来るかなあ。
Do you think Sawamura-san will go?
たぶん　来ないよ。
けれど行かなくちゃならないんだ。
Probably not. But I still have to.
Yeah. Good luck.
うん。　頑張ってね。
Katou, thanks.
加藤　ありがとな。
Huh? But I haven't done anything.
えっ？　私　何もしてないけど。
ゆうべ　頑張ったのは
霞ヶ丘先輩だし。
It was Kasumigaoka-senpai
who did all the work last night.
それでも　ありがとな。
Maybe, but thanks all the same.
そういえばさ　サークルの名前
そろそろ考えないとね。
That reminds me, we need to come up with a name for our circle soon.
Yeah, you're right.
そうだな。
それじゃ　行ってくる。
Well then, I'm off.
うん。　いってらっしゃい。
Sure. See you later.
伊織！
Iori.
Oh, my! Fancy seeing you here, Tomoya-kun!
（伊織）あれ～　倫也君。
来てたんだ。
いや　お前　さっきから
ずっと　こっち見てただろ。
Uh, you've been watching me
the whole time I've been here.
To what do I owe the honor of you coming over to our area for a visit?
（伊織）君が　うちのスペースを
訪れるなんて→
どういう風の吹き回しだい？
（伊織）言っておくけど
柏木エリの件なら手加減しないよ。
I hate to break it to you, but I don't plan on backing down on Kashiwagi Eri.
I'm not here to ask you to back down.
手加減なんて　望んじゃいないよ。
ただ　協力してもらいたいだけだ。
I just want your help.
協力？　何のだい？
My help? With what?
What else?
決まってるだろ。　俺のサークルに
英梨々を連れ戻すためだ。
With dragging Eriri back to my circle!
Servis
Erii...
Over here!
≪こっちだ！　英梨々！
Over here, Eriri!
何やってんのよ　倫也。
What are you doing, Tomoya?
ちょっと　抜け出さないか？
英梨々。
May I run away with you for a while, Eriri?
はあ？　あんた　何を…。
What's with you?
久しぶりに　俺と街に出よう！
Let's go into town together like we used to!
Let's go, Eriri!
さあ　行こう！　英梨々。
Aren't you embarrassed doing that?
やってて　恥ずかしくない？
恥ずかしいけど！
Totally embarrassed!
I could die of shame!
やってて　死にたくなるけど！
But even so, I can't die just yet!
それでも　今は　まだ
死ぬわけにはいかない！
だって　俺は
お前と仲直りするまでは→
I refuse to die until I've
patched things up with you!
死ねないからだ！
（詩羽）
《じゃあ　決行は明日の夜》→
All right, the plan will be
carried out tomorrow night.
The location will be Sawamura-san's balcony, yes?
《目的地は澤村さんの家のバルコニー
ということでいいのね？》
《あいつんち
毎年　花火大会の夜に→
Every year, her family throws a party the night of the fireworks display.
パーティーを開くんだよ》
That'll be the only opportunity
I'll have to win her back.
《だから　説得するなら
そのときしかない》
Very well.
（詩羽）《分かった。
シチュエーションは→
We'll base the situation on the fireworks display event in Little Love Rhapsody.
『リトルラブ・ラプソディ』の
花火イベントをベースにする》→
《加藤さん　そのシーン
今すぐ　プレーできるかしら？》
Katou-san, can you play that scene right now?
（恵）《はーい》
Sure.
The plan is designed to stimulate her past memories
and induce nostalgia to incite her to make up with you.
（詩羽）《彼女の昔の記憶を
ノスタルジーを刺激して→
仲直りさせる作戦よ》
Do you think it'll work?
《うまくいくかな？》
（詩羽）《大丈夫》→
Don't worry.
《なぜなら
澤村・スペンサー・英梨々の本質は→
Sawamura Spencer Eriri is by her very nature...
そう！　乙女！》→
yes, a maiden!
She's a nerdy girl waiting for her otaku prince to arrive in his white geekmobile and sweep her off her feet!
《いつか　オタクの王子様が
白い痛車に乗って→
迎えに来てくれるのを待っている
痛い女の子なのよ！》→
《アッハッハッハッ…
何？　それ》→
Can you believe that? Don't you think that's a bit
too romantic for an artist of pornographic doujin?
《エロ同人作家のくせに
夢　見過ぎなんじゃない？》
（恵）《そうかな？
エロ同人作家だからこそ→
You think? Maybe she's a romantic
because she draws pornographic doujin.
夢見がちなんじゃないかな？》
《詩羽先輩だけじゃなく加藤まで。ひどいよ》
Utaha-senpai is already enough.
Don't you join in too, Katou!
That's mean!
Shimamura Elementary School
The school building...
（英梨々）校舎…　いつの間にか
新しくなってたのね。
Looks like they've rebuilt it since we went here.
おととしだったかな。
建て替えたの。
I think they rebuilt it two years ago.
（英梨々）そう。
I see.
なあ　英梨々…。
Say, Eriri...
Why are you trying to make up with me now?
何が仲直りよ。　いまさら。→
LitRhap was the first game
that I converted you over to.
『リトラプ』は　あたしが　あんたに
初めて布教したゲームじゃない。
そうだったな。
Yeah, it was. I never knew
of dating sims before then.
俺　それまで　乙女ゲームなんて
知らなくて。
けど　やってみたら
すっげー面白くて。
But when I tried playing it, I had a blast.
（英梨々）それを　他の女の子に
布教するなんてさ→
And then you converted another girl to them.
Wouldn't you call that betrayal?
そんなの　裏切りじゃない。
英梨々…。
Eriri...
いい本に出合えてよかったね！
I'm glad you found yourself a nice book.
Not to mention, the girl who made it is both
your childhood friend and your number one disciple.
しかも　その本を作ったのが→
幼なじみで　しかも
一番弟子だったなんて。
最高だよね！
That's the dream, isn't it?
もう　あたしなんて　いらないね。
Doesn't seem like you need me anymore.
あの子をサークルに入れちゃえば
いいんだもんね。
Just bring her into your circle.
だから　もう　ほっといて。
Leave me alone.
ごめん。　詩羽先輩。
Sorry, Utaha-senpai. Sorry, Katou.
ごめん。　加藤。
Eriri, hear me out!
英梨々　聞いてくれ！
今まで言えなかったことが
あるんだ。
There's something that I've
never been able to say to you.
（英梨々）いまさら謝っても
もう遅いよ。
Apologize all you want. It's already too late.
For a long time now, I've...
俺さ　ずっと前から　お前のこと…。
あっ。　このタイミングで言うなんて
ひきょう…。
That's no fair, playing that card now!
お前のこと
すっげー　恨んでた！
I've been incredibly pissed off at you!
何が　仲直りだよ！
できるわけないだろ！
Make up with you, my ass!
How could I do that?!
俺が　いまさら
お前を許せるわけないだろ！
I can't forgive you after what you did!
（英梨々）何よ　それ…。→
What are you saying?
何よ　それ！
What's that supposed to mean?!
I'm the one who's been wronged here!
ひどいことされたの
あたしじゃない！
What crap do you think you're pulling?!
あんた
何　めちゃくちゃ言ってんのよ！
You're the one who turned your back on me!
先に俺を見限ったのは
英梨々の方じゃないか！
（倫也）《アハハ…》
（英梨々）《ウフフ…》
《ハハハ…》
《フフフ…》
Aki
Sawamura
Nerds
Otaku couple
Aki
Sawamura
Little Love Rhapsody
Class Meeting
８年前…　脱オタしたふりして→
Eight years ago,
you're the one who pretended to quit being an otaku,
made new friends, and abandoned me!
新しい友達　つくって
俺を見捨てたのは→
お前の方じゃないか！
You...
あんた…　まだ　そんなこと
根に持ってんの？
You're still holding a grudge
over a little thing like that?
How can you call that a "little thing"?!
そんなことって何だよ！
そんなことって！
（英梨々）だって
仕方ないじゃない。→
I didn't have a choice!
あのときは　ああするより
仕方なかったんじゃない！
Back then, that's the only option I had!
仕方ないで済むか！
You think that excuses it?!
Was making new friends that important to you?!
新しい友達と遊ぶのが
そんなに大事だったのかよ！
Was it more important than
being able to talk to me about anime?!
俺とアニメの話をするよりも
大事だったのかよ！
Tomoya...
倫也…。
あのときの俺にとって→
Do you have any idea how much you meant to me back then?!
お前が　どれだけ大切だったか
分かってんのかよ！
ほとんどの男子を
敵に回したんだぞ！
I'd made enemies of just about every guy!
It was all to protect what we had!
そこまでして　お前との居場所を
守ろうとしたんだぞ！
Back then, you were all I had!
あのときの俺には
お前しかいなかったんだぞ！
何年もかかって　やっと普通に
しゃべれるようになったけど→
It took years, but now I can finally talk to people normally again.
But even so, I'll never forget
how badly you treated me back then!
それでも　俺は　あのときの
お前の仕打ちを　絶対に忘れない。
That was...
（英梨々）そんなの…→
That was your fault for getting so carried away!
そんなの　１人で暴走したあんたの勝手じゃない！
Apologize!
謝れよ！
（英梨々）謝らない！→
No.
絶対に　あたし
何があっても謝らない！→
No matter what happens,
I'll never apologize to you!
だって　倫也　あたしが
どれだけ泣いたか分かってない！
You don't know how much I cried, Tomoya!
英梨々…。
（英梨々）倫也と絶交しちゃって→
Eriri...
I severed ties with you.
Then I couldn't talk to you at school anymore and had to ignore you!
学校でも話せなくなって
無視しなくちゃならなくて→
悲しくて　悔しくて　つらくて
どれだけ泣いたか！
I've cried so much over loneliness, frustration, and heartbreak.
I've suffered way more than you have!
あたしは　あんた以上に
報いを受けた！
ずっと　心の中に
ブーメランが突き刺さってる！→
All these years, I've had a
boomerang piercing my heart!
だから　謝る理由なんかない！
So I have no reason to apologize!
お前が悪いのにかよ！
（英梨々）そうよ！　悪い？
Even though it was your own fault?!
Yeah! Is that so wrong?!
Yes, it is!
だから　悪いよ！
そんなの知らない！
I couldn't care less!
You apologize to me!
それより　あんたが謝りなさいよ！何でだよ！
Why?!
Why would you choose
that girl's book over mine?!
何で　あたしの本より
あの子の本を取るのよ！
はあ！？
人気も実力も→
Huh?!
I'm more popular, more skilled,
and have known you for way longer!
倫也と知り合ってからの時間も→
あたしの方が
はるかに上じゃない！→
Why wouldn't you pick me?!
どうして
あたしを選ばないのよ！
I like what I like!
好きなものは好きなんだよ！
キャリアなんか　知るか！
The author's history makes no difference!
Izumi-chan's book excited me more!
出海ちゃんの本の方が
ワクワクするんだよ！
Are you saying I'm inferior to that girl?
私が　あの子より劣るっていうの！？そうだよ！
That's right!
お前の方が下だよ！
劣るよ！　駄目だよ！
You're beneath her!
Inferior! Not good enough!
Even with all my hard work?
こんなに努力してるのに。
死に物狂いで頑張ってるのに？
Even though I worked myself into the ground?
才能も努力も　知ったことか。
Screw talent and hard work!
The book you put out at
Summer Comiket today sucked!
今日　夏コミで出した本が
負けてんだよ　お前。
今　まさに　足りないんだよ！
すごくないんだよ！
You just don't have what it takes right now! Not even close to it!
（英梨々）
あたし　一生懸命　頑張った。→
But I worked so hard.
外では　仮面　かぶって
家で　死に物狂いで描いた。→
I put on a mask outside,
but at home I worked myself to death!
あたしたちを引き裂いた
あの連中を見返したくて…。→
I wanted to get back at the jerks who split us up!
I wanted to go back to how it was.
昔みたいに戻りたくて
やっと　ここまで来たのに…。
I thought I'd come so far.
そうだよ。
お前　ここまで来たんだよ。
You're right. You've come a long way.
速くて　うまくて
安定してきたんだよ。
You show speed, skill, and consistency.
So next, achieve greatness!
なら　次は　すごくなれよ！
速くて　うまくて　安定したまま
すごくなってみせろよ！
Let's see you become fast,
skilled, consistent, and great!
どうやって！？
How do I do that?!
This is the limit of my talent!
努力だって　才能だって
もう限界よ！
知るか　そんなの！
お前の絵だろ！　自分で考えろ！
Don't ask me! It's your art!
Figure it out yourself!
You're asking too much of me!
そんなの　むちゃくちゃよ！
そうだよ　無茶だよ！
That's right, I am!
If you don't want to take it to
the next level, you don't have to!
だから　その気がないなら
なれなくてもいいよ！
俺の一番なんか
どうだっていいだろ！
You don't care about being my number one!
Egoistic Lily
New book
Now sold out!
East Hall 5
Line Ends Here
Just watch me.
（英梨々）なる…。
えっ？
あたし
あんたの一番に　なってやる。→
I'm gonna become your number one.
それまでは　絶対に謝らない。
Until then, I'm never going to apologize.
The truth is I wish he'd hold me tight
hontou wa dakiagete hoshii
He's the one who understands me the most
wakatte kureru ichiban no hito ni
勝手にしろ。
Do what you must.
Why'd you have to let go of my hand?
ano hi doushite te wo hanashita
Now it's all in the past
tooi himitsukichi
If only I could go back
mou ichido subete wo
And do it over again
yarinaoshitai
S-So, Eriri...
But I still wouldn't forgive you
dakedo yurushite agenai
なっ…　なあ　英梨々。
（英梨々）うん？
お前　足　くじいたっての嘘だろ。
You lied about twisting your ankle, right?
I nearly lost it forever
nakushikaketan da
本当は歩けるんだろ？
You can actually walk, right?
The picture of a future we could only draw together
futari ni shika kakenasou na miraizu
王女様を
強引に連れ出した騎士様が→
A knight who forcefully pulls a princess from
her castle doesn't have any right to complain.
何　弱音　吐いてんのよ？
I won't ask you to be where I belong
ibasho ni natte tte iwanai
But it doesn't seem we've made up yet.
けど　俺たち
仲直りもしてないよな？
That'd mean showing weakness
yowasa misesou da
I guess not.
A lily blooms high and proud
lily no hana wa kedakaku blooming
そうだね。→
仲　悪いまんまだね。
あたしたち…。
We're still on the outs, aren't we?
（英梨々）できたー！
サークルカット　完成！
Finished!
The circle banner illustration's done!
おっ　見せろ　見せろ。
Show us, show us!
へえ　あなたにしては　いい感じね。澤村さん。
For you, that's almost pleasant, Sawamura-san.
…って　ちょっと待って。
Hey, wait a minute!
Is it just me, or is that girl not wearing anything?
その女の子
もしかして　服着てなくない？
It's fine, Katou-san.
大丈夫よ　加藤さん。
I think I've captured her model's figure perfectly. That is to say, your figure.
ちゃんと　モデルのあなたの体形を完璧に再現したつもりだから。
There's nothing perfect about that!
それって
完璧に大丈夫じゃないよ。
何を言ってるの？
What are you saying?
A real heroine is one who strips when told to strip
and who breathes heavily when told to breathe heavily.
脱げと言われれば脱ぎ
あえげと言われれば　あえぐのが→
本物の
ヒロインというものでしょう？
（恵）そっ　そういうものなんだ。
I-I had no idea.
いや　これ　一般ゲーだから。
Relax, this is an all-ages game.
One more thing, Tomoya.
（英梨々）それより　倫也。
最後は　ちゃんと締めなさいよ。→
Put the finishing touch on it, Producer.
プロデューサー。
ああ。
Yeah.
Blessing Software, huh?
（恵）「ｂｌｅｓｓｉｎｇ　ｓｏｆｔｗａｒｅ」か。
いい名前だろ？
Good name, huh?
Well, for you, I suppose.
まっ　あんたにしてはね。
意訳すると
「めぐみソフト」だけどね。
Though, that roughly translates to "Megumi Software" in Japanese.
えっ？
いや…　あの…。
Um, well...
I just thought...
いや　あの　その…。
After every good-bye, my cheeks are always warm
bye-bye no ato samenai binetsu
w
And as I feel the wind against them, I always think
yokaze ni fukare kangaeru
Love? Hate? Hate? Love? Over and over
suki kirai kirai suki kurikaesu
What are you seeing in those eyes of yours?
sono hitomi ni utsutteiru no wa
Reality or something 2-D?
real sore tomo nijigen
Don't just say I look pretty like it's no big deal to me
tayasuku kawaii da nante iwanai de yo ne
Tomorrow, you'll rub your eyes and say "good morning"
ashita mo me wo kosutte ohayou wo itte
And talk about all sorts of pointless stuff
tawai mo nai koto takusan oshiete
And as we slowly grow closer together
sukoshizutsu chikadzuiteku kyori ni
What do I do? What am I usually like?
doushiyou jibun ja nai mitai da
This merry-go-round just never stops
merry-go-round ga tomaranakute
Spinning, spinning, the scenery blurs by
mawaru mawaru keshiki ga kawatteku
Like a colorful dream
colorful na yume wo miru
Throb, throb, I can feel them inside
dokudoku shite karadajuu wo
Going 'round and 'round, these feelings
meguru meguru kimochi
I still can't put them into words
mada kotoba ni dekinakute
Even though one word would be enough
hitokoto sore de juubun nanoni
（出海）お兄ちゃん
柏木エリ先生と　知り合いなの？
Onii-chan, you know Kashiwagi Eri-sensei?
出海も知らないうちに
知り合いなんだけどね。
You also know her without realizing it, Izumi.
（出海）ちょっと　待ってよ。
Hey, wait a minute!
Why would an artist from a
famous circle draw something for me?
そんな有名サークルの作家さんが
何で私なんかに？
（伊織）実は　昔からの
『リトラプ』ファンで→
Actually, she says she's a long-time LitRhap fan
お前の同人誌に
感動したんだってさ。
and that your doujinshi really touched her.
Onii-chan, did you give
Kashiwagi Eri-sensei a copy of my book?!
お兄ちゃん
まさか　柏木エリ先生に→
私の本　渡したの？
Nope. It seems she stood
in line and bought it herself.
いや　自分で並んで
買ってったみたいだよ。
（出海）何で！？
挨拶してくれればいいのにー！
What?!
She should have introduced herself!
To Hashima Izumi-san
Keep up the great work!
Kashiwagi Eri
To Hashima Izumi-san
Keep up the great work!
Kashiwagi Eri
（出海）うわ～　すっご～い！
Wow!
To Hashima Izumi-san
Keep up the great work!
Kashiwagi Eri
To Hashima Izumi
I'm not about to lose to you!
You can bet your ass I'm gonna win!
Sawamura Spencer Eriri
To Hashima Izumi
I'm not about to lose to you!
You can bet your ass I'm gonna win!
Sawamura Spencer Eriri
To Hashima Izumi
I'm not about to lose to you!
You can bet your ass I'm gonna win!
Sawamura Spencer Eriri
To Hashima Izumi
I'm not about to lose to you!
You can bet your ass I'm gonna win!
Sawamura Spencer Eriri
To Hashima Izumi
I'm not about to lose to you!
You can bet your ass I'm gonna win!
Sawamura Spencer Eriri
To Hashima Izumi
I'm not about to lose to you!
You can bet your ass I'm gonna win!
Sawamura Spencer Eriri
To Hashima Izumi
I'm not about to lose to you!
You can bet your ass I'm gonna win!
Sawamura Spencer Eriri
To Hashima Izumi
I'm not about to lose to you!
You can bet your ass I'm gonna win!
Sawamura Spencer Eriri
To Hashima Izumi
I'm not about to lose to you!
You can bet your ass I'm gonna win!
Sawamura Spencer Eriri
To Hashima Izumi
I'm not about to lose to you!
You can bet your ass I'm gonna win!
Sawamura Spencer Eriri
To Hashima Izumi
I'm not about to lose to you!
You can bet your ass I'm gonna win!
Sawamura Spencer Eriri
To Hashima Izumi
I'm not about to lose to you!
You can bet your ass I'm gonna win!
Sawamura Spencer Eriri
To Hashima Izumi
I'm not about to lose to you!
You can bet your ass I'm gonna win!
Sawamura Spencer Eriri
To Hashima Izumi
I'm not about to lose to you!
You can bet your ass I'm gonna win!
Sawamura Spencer Eriri
To Hashima Izumi
I'm not about to lose to you!
You can bet your ass I'm gonna win!
Sawamura Spencer Eriri
To Hashima Izumi
I'm not about to lose to you!
You can bet your ass I'm gonna win!
Sawamura Spencer Eriri
To Hashima Izumi
I'm not about to lose to you!
You can bet your ass I'm gonna win!
Sawamura Spencer Eriri
To Hashima Izumi
I'm not about to lose to you!
You can bet your ass I'm gonna win!
Sawamura Spencer Eriri
To Hashima Izumi
I'm not about to lose to you!
You can bet your ass I'm gonna win!
Sawamura Spencer Eriri
To Hashima Izumi
I'm not about to lose to you!
You can bet your ass I'm gonna win!
Sawamura Spencer Eriri
To Hashima Izumi
I'm not about to lose to you!
You can bet your ass I'm gonna win!
Sawamura Spencer Eriri
To Hashima Izumi
I'm not about to lose to you!
You can bet your ass I'm gonna win!
Sawamura Spencer Eriri
To Hashima Izumi
I'm not about to lose to you!
You can bet your ass I'm gonna win!
Sawamura Spencer Eriri
To Hashima Izumi
I'm not about to lose to you!
You can bet your ass I'm gonna win!
Sawamura Spencer Eriri
To Hashima Izumi
I'm not about to lose to you!
You can bet your ass I'm gonna win!
Sawamura Spencer Eriri
To Hashima Izumi
I'm not about to lose to you!
You can bet your ass I'm gonna win!
Sawamura Spencer Eriri
To Hashima Izumi
I'm not about to lose to you!
You can bet your ass I'm gonna win!
Sawamura Spencer Eriri
To Hashima Izumi
I'm not about to lose to you!
You can bet your ass I'm gonna win!
Sawamura Spencer Eriri
To Hashima Izumi
I'm not about to lose to you!
You can bet your ass I'm gonna win!
Sawamura Spencer Eriri
To Hashima Izumi
I'm not about to lose to you!
You can bet your ass I'm gonna win!
Sawamura Spencer Eriri
To Hashima Izumi
I'm not about to lose to you!
You can bet your ass I'm gonna win!
Sawamura Spencer Eriri
To Hashima Izumi
I'm not about to lose to you!
You can bet your ass I'm gonna win!
Sawamura Spencer Eriri
To Hashima Izumi
I'm not about to lose to you!
You can bet your ass I'm gonna win!
Sawamura Spencer Eriri
To Hashima Izumi
I'm not about to lose to you!
You can bet your ass I'm gonna win!
Sawamura Spencer Eriri
To Hashima Izumi
I'm not about to lose to you!
You can bet your ass I'm gonna win!
Sawamura Spencer Eriri
To Hashima Izumi
I'm not about to lose to you!
You can bet your ass I'm gonna win!
Sawamura Spencer Eriri
To Hashima Izumi
I'm not about to lose to you!
You can bet your ass I'm gonna win!
Sawamura Spencer Eriri
To Hashima Izumi
I'm not about to lose to you!
You can bet your ass I'm gonna win!
Sawamura Spencer Eriri
To Hashima Izumi
I'm not about to lose to you!
You can bet your ass I'm gonna win!
Sawamura Spencer Eriri
To Hashima Izumi
I'm not about to lose to you!
You can bet your ass I'm gonna win!
Sawamura Spencer Eriri
To Hashima Izumi
I'm not about to lose to you!
You can bet your ass I'm gonna win!
Sawamura Spencer Eriri
To Hashima Izumi
I'm not about to lose to you!
You can bet your ass I'm gonna win!
Sawamura Spencer Eriri
To Hashima Izumi
I'm not about to lose to you!
You can bet your ass I'm gonna win!
Sawamura Spencer Eriri
To Hashima Izumi
I'm not about to lose to you!
You can bet your ass I'm gonna win!
Sawamura Spencer Eriri
To Hashima Izumi
I'm not about to lose to you!
You can bet your ass I'm gonna win!
Sawamura Spencer Eriri
To Hashima Izumi
I'm not about to lose to you!
You can bet your ass I'm gonna win!
Sawamura Spencer Eriri
I'm not about to lose to you!
To Hashima Izumi
You can bet your ass I'm gonna win!
I'm not about to lose to you!
Sawamura Spencer Eriri
To Hashima Izumi
I'm not about to lose to you!
You can bet your ass I'm gonna win!
Sawamura Spencer Eriri
To Hashima Izumi
I'm not about to lose to you!
You can bet your ass I'm gonna win!
Sawamura Spencer Eriri
To Hashima Izumi
You can bet your ass I'm gonna win!
Sawamura Spencer Eriri
I'm not about to lose to you!
You can bet your ass I'm gonna win!
Sawamura Spencer Eriri
To Hashima Izumi
I'm not about to lose to you!
Sawamura Spencer Eriri
To Hashima Izumi
You can bet your ass I'm gonna win!
I'm not about to lose to you!
Sawamura Spencer Eriri
To Hashima Izumi
You can bet your ass I'm gonna win!
I'm not about to lose to you!
Sawamura Spencer Eriri
To Hashima Izumi
I'm not about to lose to you!
You can bet your ass I'm gonna win!
Sawamura Spencer Eriri
I'm not about to lose to you!
You can bet your ass I'm gonna win!
Sawamura Spencer Eriri
To Hashima Izumi
I'm not about to lose to you!
You can bet your ass I'm gonna win!
Sawamura Spencer Eriri
To Hashima Izumi
I'm not about to lose to you!
You can bet your ass I'm gonna win!
To Hashima Izumi
Sawamura Spencer Eriri
I'm not about to lose to you!
You can bet your ass I'm gonna win!
Sawamura Spencer Eriri
To Hashima Izumi
I'm not about to lose to you!
You can bet your ass I'm gonna win!
Sawamura Spencer Eriri
I'm not about to lose to you!
To Hashima Izumi
You can bet your ass I'm gonna win!
I'm not about to lose to you!
Sawamura Spencer Eriri
To Hashima Izumi
I'm not about to lose to you!
You can bet your ass I'm gonna win!
Sawamura Spencer Eriri
To Hashima Izumi
I'm not about to lose to you!
You can bet your ass I'm gonna win!
Sawamura Spencer Eriri
To Hashima Izumi
I'm not about to lose to you!
Sawamura Spencer Eriri
To Hashima Izumi
You can bet your ass I'm gonna win!
I'm not about to lose to you!
Sawamura Spencer Eriri
To Hashima Izumi
I'm not about to lose to you!
You can bet your ass I'm gonna win!
Sawamura Spencer Eriri
To Hashima Izumi
I'm not about to lose to you!
You can bet your ass I'm gonna win!
Sawamura Spencer Eriri